And that's it.
With this, at long last...
It's finally...
complete!
One melon and yakisoba bread!
Cream bread please! Cream bread!
Pshuu...
Pshuuu...
One egg salad sandwich.
Here, one egg salad sandwich.
I finally...
I finally bought it!
Good job.
I wasn't sure if you'd be able to buy one
on your own before you graduated.
This is on the house.
Thanks!
Sophy bought herself bread without our help.
Chanko!
The Man From Brazil.
This monja riceball is delicious!
If you say so, Dorothy.
Aren't you going to eat it?
I got this plum rice ball from the lady running the lunch stand, but...
Would you like it, Laala?
You sure?
Yeah! Awesome!
Here.
I only have Red Flash before concerts.
Then I'll help myself.
Thanks!
Sour!
That reminds me, Head Disciplinarian Minami
already had herself a solo concert.
How unfair!
That's 'cause our spineless manager
has holed himself up in a beauty parlor.
If Dressing Pafé reforms,
that curse will take away my handsomeness-usa!
There's no way I'll let that happen-usa!
Anti-aging-usa!
Kuma and Usagi both believe in this curse.
How strange.
That stupid Usagi has gone weak in the knees.
How pathetic.
Once convinced, there's no changing his mind.
At this point, anything we say
goes in one ear and out the other.
I wonder what kind of curse it is.
So you're afraid of curses.
What a chicken, Laala!
I'm sorry I made fun of curses!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
What was that?
Even a moment of weakness can prove fatal in the jungle.
It silently circles around behind its prey,
ready to strike at any moment.
Awesome!
A gold medal!
What's with you, old man?!
Don't sneak up on us!
These are school grounds.
Outsiders are prohibited from entering here.
My my my.
Calm yourselves.
I am no stranger.
I'm only here to hug my truly beloved Sophy.
Forcing a hug on a young lady...
Is inexcusable!
How repulsive!
Regardless of how passionate a fan you are...
This is absurd, old man.
It's a principal's duty to protect their students!
This shall not go unpunished!
Um...
Please stop.
Huh?
That's...
my father.
Huh?!
What?!
Please excuse us.
We had no idea you were her father.
We're sorry.
Well, I had to find Sophy as soon as I could,
and rushed straight here from the airport.
Of course my actions made it look strange.
He's completely different from you, Sophy.
I take after my mother.
Unlike myself, my father's full of energy.
After all, he's an adventurer.
What?
Adventurer?
Here's my card.
Ah, let's see here.
King of Adventure, Location: Earth?
When you're an adventurer, every day is full of excitement!
Taking killer pictures on the back of a killer whale,
owling in a giant owl sleeping bag,
tagging a tiger,
being pigged up on by a bunch of pigs...
Your gags are beyond the max!
Principal, I've brought you a souvenir.
A-A snake?!
It's fake made out of rubber.
Since it has a zipper along the side of it, it's great for storing bamboo poles.
Y-Yeah...
To be honest, we've been separated for quite some time,
but now we'll be able to live together once agian.
That's what I came to tell her.
Oh?
Isn't that great, Sophy?!
Since I lack the physical strength,
my father has been flying around the world in search of the legendary powerful plum.
Powerful plum?
That's right!
When it comes to its power,
it's said that one can run 30,000 meters with just one,
making it the ultimate plum!
Wow!
However, even after ten long years,
I still haven't found that legendary powerful plum.
But I'll never give up!
If I can't find it, I'll just make it myself!
That's when I purchased a stockpile of legendary-grade
plum seeds from a Brazilian merchant.
Her dad sure is decisive.
I require precise calculations,
so we're complete opposites in that regard.
Do not fear failure!
Challenge yourself!
Those are my mottos.
That is why I give you this, madam...
Yes yes...
A tr-transfer notification?!
What?!
Hold on, Father!
I don't remember anything about transfer---
Are you surprised, Sophy?
Your father has created Prifornia,
a 10,000 hectare plum plantation.
Prifornia?
What prefecture is that in?
It's another country.
What?!
That means Sophy's going to another country?!
Sophy and I will be leaving Japan next week.
And we'll arrive just in time to have the plum flowers greet you in full bloom, Sophy.
Sophy...
Are you really going to Prifornia?
I don't know.
Making Drama Switch On!
Wondrous Angel à la mode!
I'll help myself.
Ahh!
Delicious!
Yummy!
Cyalume Change!
You're full-blown celebrities-nekon.
I'm thrilled.
Of course we are.
After all, our destiny is to become Divine Idols.
Next up is SoLaMi SMILE's hit concert
from before they broke up.
The three of them get along perfectly!
Exactly what I'd expect of SoLaMi Smile.
However, according to my research,
Sophy's dad has returned home and
asked her to live with him in Prifornia.
There's plenty of time.
Aroma Prophecy Grimoire, chapter 8, section 184:
"Recall the lightening which tears the sky."
Derodero derosaimu.
While it seems to trouble thee,
I'll say that SoLaMi Smile is not a proper fit for thee.
I hath seen what thine future has in store.
I won't go into the unfortunate details,
but it would be to thy advantage to break away from SoLaMi Smile.
Break away from SoLaMi Smile?
If ye continue to team up with the overly powerful Laala and Mirei,
thine presence shall continue to dwindle.
That is, so to say, a step toward becoming an invisible idol.
Hey there!
I'm Mikan the angel!
Spending time abroad with your father sounds wonderful.
If you go abroad, things like pizza and
hamburgers will be bigger and more fun to eat.
I'd be totally jelly!
Pitiful lamb, worry about it!
Yes, be troubled!
When people are struggling and
suffering with their problems,
that is the greatest feast for us.
Demon Demon Deruderu Beam!
Jello-jello Angel!
So this is where you've been, Sophy.
What is it?
My father's been searching for a
powerful plum for me for ten years,
and he's finally found some.
Yeah.
I love my father.
Hey, Sophy, you know how we're doing our best to reform SoLaMi Smile, right?
Yeah.
Well, if living together with your father
that you love so much will make you happy,
I won't stop you.
I'll support you all the way!
Laala...
I feel the same way-pri.
Don't worry about us.
You should choose the path that you want-pri!
That I...
I don't want to go to Prifornia!
I want to continue doing PriPara with you two!
Sophy!
Thanks!
That makes me really happy-pri!
Now you just need to tell
your father how you truly feel.
Yeah, but I don't want to see
my beloved father saddened.
You're family.
You shouldn't keep anything from each other.
You have to properly tell him your feelings.
Your father did it because he wanted to-pri.
I'm sure he'll understand-pri.
Laala, Mirei, thanks.
I'll...
...go tell my father my feelings.
You here, Honey?
Ah, welcome back-nekon.
The usual-kuma.
Kuma?!
Why are you here?!
I should be saying the same thing-usa!
Wha'd you say?!
Would the two of you care for bratcurse?
Bratcurse?
Bratwurst.
You scared us-kuma!
We're quite sensitive to the word "curse" as of late-kuma.
Though, I'll take one-kuma.
Of course.
Just give me a moment-nekon.
Because my accursed movements are a little slow.
A curse?!
It's cute how scared you get-nekon.
This is the Prifornia plum plantation that we'll be living at.
What do you think? It's huge, isn't it?
Father...
To tell you the truth, I...
There's nothing to worry about.
Your father will handle all of
the heavy lifting at the plantation.
That's not it.
Huh?
I don't want to go to Prifornia!
There are still things I want to do here!
Sophy, explain it to me slowly.
Huh?
What's this?
I'm in the middle of a complicated discussion...
What?!
You're kidding?!
Now then, I'll go comfort myself
at Neko Cafe again today-kuma.
Kuma.
Huh?
Enter me into a concert.
Kuma?
Sophy's doing a solo concert?
You said Lady Sophy's having a solo concert?!
Chanko!
It appears buying bread at the school cafe wasn't enough.
Now she's trying to do a solo concert on her own.
We, her Royal Guard, will cheer Sophy on...
with the ultimate cheer we've been working on chanko!
Chanko!
Lady Sophy...
is life!
What?!
You're kidding?!
What happened, Father?!
It's already done for.
Although the several hundred seeds I planted have bloomed,
there wasn't a single plum to be found;
they were all cherries.
Father!
Are you okay?
Pull yourself together, Father.
He just naturally goes at cosmic speed,
and never stops to think things through.
How unfortunate, Father.
He might not be able to get back on his feet quickly like he normally does.
I...
Please scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your coord.
Coord Change Start!
A late blooming sakura coord decorated with cherry blossoms in full bloom.
The dyed purple sakura leaves add to the cool taste that fits your image.
Flower Blossom Floral Coord!
I love you, Lady Sophy!
So cool!
So beautiful!
Have you been good, my little cagebirds?
Yes!
You're lying.
I have prepared the perfect song for you bad little girls.
"Solar Flare Sherbet Sakura Shower Version".
Sophy!
S-Sophy...
You've got this much energy now?!
Doing concerts with PriPara is her energy.
Making Drama Switch On!
Plums, peaches...
Cherry blossoms in full bloom!
Liberation Maiden Primavera!
Cyalume Change!
Cheer up, Father. Sakura and plums are both plums.
S-Sophy!
Purple, huh?
Miss Sophy is a Cool-type idol, of course.
You're really heading back already?
Even though I wasn't able to get dried plums,
the cherry trees will grow cherries.
I need to rush back and harvest them.
That's what your concert taught me, Sophy.
Father...
Thank you for that splendid concert.
You've always lacked physical strength, Sophy.
But with the energetic concert you put on with everyone's support,
you've made your old man proud enough he could ascend.
Sophy, do your best at PriPara,
and become a divine idol!
Thank you, Father.
Laala, Mirei,
please continue to look after my daughter.
Will do!
Bye!
Pushuu~.
Sophy!
Pushuu.
My oh my,
you really did a cosmic job this time!
Sohpie, are you okay?
The SoLaMi Smile break-up strategy was a complete failure-nekon.
Her flower filled concert was spectacular!
But Mikan likes meat buns more than flowers!
The prophecy was a failure.
Now that it's come to this, I shall consult the forbidden and most horrific prophecy!
The next prophecy; chapter 7, section 666:
"The one with crimson eyes strikes back."
If I turn the large number of mega-nees into zombies,
SoLaMi Smile will...
No, I'll be able to take down everyone in PriPara!
Demon Demon Deruderu Beam!
There's a problem-kuma!
Do you think you can do a concert
at the Dream Theatre-kuma?
We don't even have a five person team yet!
It has been decided you will have your debut live at the theater's completion ceremony-kuma.
However, the catch is,
you have to win the sports festival.
Capisce!
We'll win and reform!
Wait, if you do that, the curse...
I'm in trouble-kuma!
Next time:
First to the Dream Theatre-kuma!
Aim for your dreams!
Let's go PriPara!